schools9india.com 2015-02-27

# Privacy Policy Terms for schools9india

###  Privacy Policy Terms for schools9india 

###  PRIVACY POLICY

** ** _ **Privacy Policy for  www.schools9india.com**_

At www.schools9india.com the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us.

Schools9india.com may from time to time collect names and/or details of website visitors. This may include the mailing list, blog comments sections and in various sections of the www.schools9india.com site.These details will not be passed onto any other third party or other organization unless we are required to by government or other law enforcement authority.

If you contribute content, such as discussion comments, to the site, your contribution may be publicly displayed including personally identifiable information.

www.schools9india.com links to independently run web sites outside of the www.schools9india.com domain. We take no responsibility for the privacy practices or content of such web sites.

www.schools9india.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

www.schools9india.com uses cookies to save login details and to collect statistical information about the numbers of visitors to the site.

_**Double Click DART Cookie:**_

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.schools9india.com.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.schools9india.com and other sites on the Internet.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.schools9india.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.schools9india.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.schools9india.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

This policy will be updated from time to time. If we make significant changes to this policy after that time a notice will be posted on the main pages of the website.
